[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this vector dice
你可以创建这个矢量骰子
illustration
图解
using inkscape and if you'd like to
使用Inkscape，如果您愿意
learn more about how inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class
班级
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where i go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape
Inkscape中的功能
and i explain what they are and
我解释了它们是什么，
demonstrate how they work i'll have a
演示它们是如何工作的，我会有一个
link in the description of the video if
视频描述中的链接，如果
you want to check that out
你想去看看吗？
so to get get us started here in
所以为了让我们在这里开始
inkscape the first thing we want to do
Inkscape我们想要做的第一件事
is set up our documents so that we are
就是设置我们的文件，这样我们就可以
all working with a similar workflow
都使用类似的工作流程
to do that we'll come up here to where
为了做到这一点，我们将来到这里
it says view make sure you have custom
它说查看确保您有习惯
selected
已选择
and then we'll come up here to where it
然后我们会来到这里
says zoom and zoom in at one to one
表示按1比1的比例放大和放大
and then up here in the snapping menu i
然后在上面的捕捉菜单中我
just want to click this icon over here
我只想点击这里的这个图标
to the top left that says enable
在左上角显示启用
snapping as you can see i already have
如你所见，我已经这样做了
it enabled
它启用了
and these are the options we're going to
这些是我们要做的选择
want enabled for this tutorial right
希望为本教程正确启用
here where it says
在这里，它说
snap nodes pads and handles enable that
捕捉节点垫和手柄可以实现这一点
and then over here where it says
然后在这里，上面写着
snap to cusp nodes and then right next
捕捉到尖点节点，然后右键下一步
to it where it says snap to smooth nodes
到其中显示捕捉到平滑结点的位置
and once we've done that i'm going to
一旦我们做到这一点，我就会
open up the align and distribute menu
打开对齐并分布菜单
with this icon
带着这个图标
over here or you can press ctrl shift a
在这里，或者您可以按Ctrl Shift a
where it says relative to i want to set
它说的是相对于我想要设置
that to last selected
最后一次选择的
and then i'll open up the um fill and
然后我会打开这个填充物
stroke menu over here with this icon or
此处有此图标的笔划菜单或
you can press ctrl
您可以按Ctrl键
shift and f on your keyboard to get that
按键盘上的Shift和f键就可以了
open so once we have that open the first
打开，一旦我们打开了第一个
thing we want to do is create a polygon
我们要做的是创建一个多边形
so i'm going to come over here to the
所以我要到这里来
stars and polygons tool
星形和多边形工具
and over here from these settings i want
在这里，从这些环境中我想要
to choose polygon rather than star
选择多边形而不是星形
where it says corners i want to make
上面写着我想做的角落
sure we have six and then rounded and
当然，我们有六个，然后四舍五入
randomized both set to zero as you can
随机化后，两者都尽可能设置为零
see i already have these values
看，我已经有了这些值
set beforehand you will probably have to
事先设定好，你很可能不得不
change these manually so go ahead and
手动更改这些设置，因此请继续并
type those in
将这些内容输入
and once you do that just click and drag
一旦这样做了，只需点击并拖动
on the canvas to create a polygon i'm
在画布上创建一个多边形
going to hold ctrl
要按住Ctrl键
and then click and drag the mouse up
然后点击并向上拖动鼠标
like that so that it creates the polygon
这样它就创建了一个多边形
where the points
其中的要点是
are going vertically as opposed to
是垂直的，而不是
horizontally
水平地
that right there is what we're looking
这就是我们要找的东西
for once we've done that i'm going to
这一次我们做到了这一点我要
take this move this towards the center
把这一步移到中心
of the page
页面的
i want to bring the opacity of this down
我想把这件事的不透明性降下来
a little bit i'm going to take this
有点，我要拿着这个
opacity over here and just drop that
不透明的东西放在这里，把它放下
down roughly in half and i'm going to
大体减半，我要
scale this down a little bit i'm going
再缩小一点，我要走了
to hold ctrl and shift
按住Ctrl和Shift键
and just click and drag to scale that
只需点击并拖动即可进行缩放
down
降下来
what i want to do now is duplicate so
我现在想做的是复制，所以
i'm going to right click this and go to
我要右键单击它，然后转到
duplicate
复本
and i'm going to click and drag this up
我要点击并将其拖上来
here until these two corners snap so we
在这里，直到这两个角落断裂，所以我们
get something like this here where
在哪里买到这样的东西？
there's this diamond shape intersecting
有一个钻石形状的交叉点
between the two of them
在他们两个之间
and i want to make this red just so we
我想把这个染成红色，这样我们
can differentiate it from the original
可以将它与原始的区分开来
then i want to duplicate that object
然后我想复制那个对象
again i'm going to right click that and
我再一次右击它，然后
go to duplicate
转到复制
come over here snap this over to the
到这里来，把这个放到
left side over here
左边在这里
and then do that one more time right
然后再做一次，对吗
click duplicate
单击复制
and snap this one over to this right
把这个扣到这个右边
side like that and with this red
像那样的一边，还有这个红色
polygon still selected i'm going to go
多边形仍被选中，我要去
to edit
编辑
select same and click on fill color
选择相同并点击填充颜色
it's going to select all of the objects
它将选择所有对象
on your canvas that have the same
在你的画布上有相同的
red fill which is these three objects
红色填充是这三个对象
right here and i want to combine those
就在这里，我想把这些结合起来
together by going to path
一起走上小路
combine and once we've done that i just
结合在一起，一旦我们做到了，我就
want to click and drag over
想要单击并拖动到
the entire thing entirely like that so
整件事就是这样的
we have everything selected including
我们什么都选好了，包括
the red
红色的
object and the original polygon in there
对象和其中的原始多边形
and then go to path
然后转到Path
division and what's going to happen
组织和将会发生的事情
after you do that you can click off of
完成此操作后，您可以单击
the graphic to deselect everything
取消选择所有内容的图形
you'll notice this has been broken up
你会注意到这个已经被打碎了
into three individual parts here so let
在这里分成三个独立的部分
me just undo that by hitting ctrl
我只需按下Ctrl键即可撤消该操作
z now what i'm going to do is i'm going
Z现在我要做的是我要去
to create three
要创建三个
individual sides for the dice here so to
这里的骰子是单边的，所以
do that i'm going to grab the squares
做到这一点，我要去拿正方形
and rectangles tool
和矩形工具
and i'm going to hold ctrl and shift on
我要按住Ctrl键和Shift键
the keyboard and i'm going to click and
键盘和我要点击并
drag to create a perfectly symmetrical
拖动可创建完全对称的
square like that
像这样的正方形
and since this square is going to
由于这个广场将会是
represent one of the sides of the dice
代表骰子的一面
what i want to do is round the corners
我想做的就是绕过街角
of this because as i demonstrated in the
因为正如我在
um
恩
in the thumbnail the dice has rounded
在缩略图中，骰子已经变圆了
corners so i'm going to take this little
所以我要把这一小块
handle up here to the top right this
从这里到右上角的这个
circle node
圆形节点
i'm just going to click and drag that
我只需点击并拖动它
down like that so we get some nice
像这样下去，这样我们就能得到一些好的
rounded
舍入
nice rounded corners like that and now i
像这样漂亮的圆角，现在我
want to create circles for the inside of
我想要为内部创建圆
this
这
rectangle that represent the number on
上的数字的矩形
the dice so i'm going to grab the
掷骰子，所以我要抓住
circles and ellipses tool
圆和椭圆工具
hold ctrl and shift and click and drag
按住Ctrl键和Shift键并单击并拖动
to create a perfectly round circle like
创建一个完美的圆形，就像
that
那
i want to make this a different color so
我想把这个改成不同的颜色
i'll make this green
我会把它做成绿色的
let me grab the select tool place this
让我拿起选择工具，把这个放在
over here in the center
就在这里的中心
i mean the top left right click that go
我的意思是左上角右键点击开始
to duplicate
复制
hold control click and drag this over to
按住Ctrl键单击并将其拖动到
the right and the reason why i'm holding
我持有的权利和原因
control is because it's locking it onto
控件是因为它将其锁定在
the vertical axis like that
像这样的垂直轴
and then i want to hold shift and click
然后我想按住Shift键并单击
on the other one so we have them both
在另一个上，所以我们两个都有
selected
已选择
right click that go to duplicate hold
右键单击转到复制暂挂
control click and drag these ones down
Ctrl单击并向下拖动这些按钮
here
这里
and then click off of it to deselect
然后将其关闭以取消选择
everything and then just take one of
所有的东西，然后只需要拿一个
these right here
这些就在这里
right click them and go to duplicate and
右键单击它们，然后转到复制和
then hold shift
然后按住Shift键
and click on the red rectangle so that
然后点击红色矩形，这样就可以
you have the circle and the green
你有圆圈和绿色
rectangle uh the red rectangle selected
矩形呃所选的红色矩形
and center them up
并把它们放在中心
on the vertical and horizontal axis like
在垂直轴和水平轴上，如
that
那
now if you notice here i made my circles
现在，如果你注意到我做了我的圆圈
a little too big so what i'm going to do
有点太大了，所以我要做的是
is i'm just going to click and drag over
我只是要点击并拖动到
those circles
那些圆圈
hold ctrl and scale those down a little
按住Ctrl键并将其缩小一点
bit
比特
i'll take this one hold shift click on
我将接受这个按住Shift键的按钮
both of those
这两个都是
click and drag these down here click off
点击并将它们拖到这里点击关闭
of the deselect
被取消选择的
i'll take these ones as well again shift
我也要这些，再换一次班
clicking them so we select them both
单击它们，这样我们就可以同时选择它们
bring them over here
把他们带到这里来
and let me try this again i'll take this
让我再试一次，我要这个。
one in the center hold shift
中间的一个按住Shift键
click on the uh the red rectangle there
点击呃那里的红色矩形
center it up on the vertical and
在垂直方向居中，
horizontal axis
水平轴
that's good now we can click off of that
这很好，现在我们可以点击它了
now we want to do is just make sure that
现在我们要做的就是确保
we have these green ones in the corners
我们在角落里有这些绿色的
centered up as well so let me click on
也居中，所以让我点击
the green one right here
就在这里的那个绿色的
hold shift click on the other four on
按住Shift键并单击其他四个打开
all four of them and group them together
全部四个，并将它们组合在一起
by clicking this button that says group
通过点击此按钮，该按钮显示为组
selected objects
选定对象
or you could press ctrl g and then hold
或者，您可以按Ctrl g，然后按住
shift and click on the red rectangle and
按住Shift并单击红色矩形，然后
just center those up on the vertical and
把它们放在垂直的中心，然后
horizontal axis like that
像这样的水平轴
and then we can go ahead and ungroup
然后我们就可以继续解组了
them so this right here is going to
他们，所以这里将会是
represent one of the sides of the dice
代表骰子的一面
now i want to do what i want to do is
现在我想做的是我想做的
create two more sides
再创建两个边
so to do that i'm going to click and
要做到这一点，我要点击并
drag over all of these
将所有这些拖到上面
and i want to duplicate them by going to
我想通过以下方式复制它们
right click by right clicking and going
通过右键单击并移动来单击鼠标右键
to duplicate
复制
then hold ctrl and just click and drag
然后按住Ctrl键并单击并拖动
this over here to the right
这个就在这里右边
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
i'm just going to delete these two
我只是要删除这两个
circles right here i'm going to
就在这里打圈，我要
click on it to select it and press
点击将其选中，然后按
delete same thing over here press delete
在这里删除相同的东西按Delete
so then we end up with the number three
所以我们最终得到了数字3
and then finally i will create one more
最后，我会再创造一个
of these
其中
right click it go to duplicate hold ctrl
右键单击它，转到复制按住Ctrl
click and drag it to the right
单击并将其拖到右侧
click off of it to deselect and then get
单击该选项以取消选择，然后获取
rid of these on the uh
把这些东西扔在呃
on the sides here so that we have just
在这里的侧面，所以我们只有
the one in the middle
中间的那个
so what i'm going to do now is i'm going
所以我现在要做的是我要去
to select all of these green ones right
把所有这些绿色的都选对
here i'm going to click and drag over
在这里，我将单击并拖动到
those green
那些绿色的
objects to make sure you just select the
对象，以确保您只选择
green object make sure you don't
绿色物体确保你不会
select the red object as well so like
也选择红色对象，如下所示
just the green objects right there
就在那里的绿色物体
unify them together by going to path
通过转到Path将它们统一在一起
union
友联市
and then hold shift and click on the red
然后按住Shift键并单击红色
rectangle and go to
矩形并转到
path difference and i want to do the
路径差异和我想要做的
same thing over here select all of these
同样的，在这里，选择所有这些
go to path union hold shift click on the
转到路径联合按住Shift键单击
red rectangle and go to path
红色矩形并转到路径
difference and then finally i'll come
不同，然后最后我会来的
over here click on the green circle
在这里，点击绿色圆圈
hold shift click on the red rectangle we
按住Shift键并单击我们的红色矩形
don't have to do a union on these ones
不需要在这些问题上进行联合
because it's just one object
因为它只是一个物体
and go to path difference so now we have
然后转到路径差，所以现在我们有
our three sides to the dice here so i'm
我们掷骰子的三面，所以我
going to
要去
click and drag over all of these let me
点击并拖动所有这些让我
hold ctrl and shift and scale these down
按住Ctrl键和Shift键并将其缩小
and i want to place these over where
我想把这些放在哪里
they're going to be implemented so i'm
它们将被实施，所以我
going to take this top one the number
我要把这个最上面的作为号码。
five put this on top
五个人把这个放在上面
i'm going to take this over here the
我要把这个拿到这里来
number three put this on the left
三号把这个放在左边
and i'll take the number one and put
我要选1号，然后把
this on the right over here what i'm
右边的这个就是我
going to do is
接下来要做的是
change the perspective of each of these
改变其中每一个的视角
objects so that they fit within this
对象，以便它们适合此
polygon
多边形
so let me zoom in on this by holding
所以让我通过按住它来放大这个
ctrl and rolling up the mouse wheel
按住Ctrl键并滚动鼠标滚轮
let me click on just this red rectangle
让我点击这个红色的矩形
right here and go to
就在这里，然后转到
path path effects and it's going to open
路径路径效果，它将打开
up the path effects menu there it is
在路径效果菜单上，它就在那里
right there
就在那里
and with the path effects menu open i'm
在打开路径效果菜单的情况下
going to press the plus icon
我要按加号图标
and what i'm looking for is perspective
我在寻找的是观点
so i'm going to come up here to where
所以我要到这里来
the search icon is i'm going to start
搜索图标是我要开始
typing
打字
p-e-r-s and there we go perspective
P-E-R-S和我们开始透视
envelope that's what we want
这就是我们想要的信封
and once we've done that come over here
一旦我们做完了，就到这里来
to the edit paths by nodes tool
转到按结点编辑路径工具
and what we're looking for right here if
我们现在要找的是如果
you notice there's different there's two
你注意到这里有两个不同的
different types of nodes there's gray
不同类型的结点为灰色
nodes
节点
inside of the object and then there's
在物体内部，然后是
white nodes on the corners what we're
角落里的白色节点，我们是什么
looking for
寻找
is the white nodes on the corners that
是角上的白色节点，
allows us to change the perspective so
使我们能够改变视角，因此
let me zoom back out
让我把镜头拉回原处
again to zoom in and out i'm just
再一次放大和缩小我只是
holding ctrl and rolling up and down the
按住Ctrl键并上下滚动
mouse wheel
鼠标滚轮
to move the page around i'm just
把书页翻来翻去我只是
pressing down the mouse wheel and moving
按下鼠标滚轮并移动
the mouse
鼠标
let me take this white node and snap
让我拿起这个白色节点，然后抓拍
this into the
这一点进入了
bottom corner of this top object let me
这个顶端物体的底角让我
take this white node and snap that into
取下这个白色节点，并将其卡入
there
那里
take this node snap it into there and
拿着这个节点，把它扣进那里
then this one
然后是这个
into there like that and now i will
就像那样，现在我会的
finalize that by going to path
通过转到Path来最终确定这一点
object to path now let's do the same
对象到路径，现在让我们做同样的事情
thing over here let's click on this
这里的东西，让我们点击这个
go to uh we're going to come over here
去，呃，我们要来这里
to the path effects menu
添加到路径效果菜单
click on the uh the plus button right
点击呃加号按钮向右
here
这里
we're going to add perspective envelope
我们要添加透视封套
and do the same thing i'm going to take
做我要做的同样的事情
this corner and snap it into here
在这个角落，然后把它卡进这里
take this corner snap it into here
拿着这个角，把它扣进这里
this corner goes down here and this
这个拐角从这里走下去，然后这个
corner goes in here
拐角从这里进去
and again finalize that by going to path
并再次通过转到Path来最终确定这一点
object to path
对象到路径
and then i will do the same thing for
然后我会为你做同样的事情
this object as well so let me select
这个对象也是如此，所以让我选择
that
那
add a new path effect perspective
添加新的路径效果透视
envelope
信封
and then snap these to their respective
然后将这些扣合到它们各自的
corners as well
拐角也一样
i'll put this one down there and then
我会把这个放在那里，然后
again we're going to finalize this by
再一次，我们将通过以下方式完成此操作
going to
要去
path object to path
路径对象到路径
so let me zoom out a little bit i'm
所以让我把镜头放大一点，我是
going to hold ctrl roll down the mouse
要按住Ctrl键，鼠标滚下
will zoom out let me grab the select
将缩小，让我抓取选择
tool
工具
what i want to do now is put a little
我现在想做的是放一点
bit of space between these three sides
这三面之间有一点空隙
because they're all touching each other
因为他们都在互相抚摸
which is not
这并不是
visually correct for what we're trying
对于我们正在尝试的内容，视觉上是正确的
to create so let me select each of these
为了创建这样，让我选择其中的每一个
red objects by shift-clicking them
按住Shift键并单击红色对象
and then just move them off of the uh
然后就把它们从呃
the polygon
多边形
for for a brief moment and i want to
因为有那么一刻，我想
reduce their size by 95
将它们的大小减少95%
so i want to come up here to where it
所以我想要到这里来
says width and height or w and h
表示宽度和高度或w和h
i want to turn on the lock right here so
我想打开这里的锁，所以
it locks the proportions as we scale it
当我们缩放它时，它会锁定比例
and right here these units of
就在这里，这些单位
measurement where it says px i'm going
测量显示PX我要去的地方
to change that to percentage
要将其更改为百分比
and i'm going to change the width to 95
我要把宽度更改为95
so we're going to reduce the size by 95
所以我们要把大小减少95%
i mean by 5 hit enter and then just
我的意思是按5下Enter键，然后
change that back to pixel so that you
将其改回像素，这样您就可以
can
能
use that later on and then let me click
稍后使用它，然后让我点击
off of that to deselect everything
以取消选择所有内容
i want to take this object right here
我想把这个东西拿在这里
hold shift click on the left side of the
按住Shift键并在左侧单击
polygon
多边形
center it up on the vertical and
在垂直方向居中，
horizontal axis do the same thing over
水平轴做同样的事情
here take this right
这里，把这个拿好
right side object hold shift click on
右侧对象按住Shift键并单击
the polygon
多边形
center it up on the vertical and
在垂直方向居中，
horizontal axis and then finally the
水平轴，最后是
same thing over here we're going to
我们在这里也要做同样的事情
center it up
居中对齐
on the vertical and horizontal axis and
在垂直轴和水平轴上
that's what we're looking for right
这就是我们正在寻找的，对的
there a little bit of space between
两者之间有一点空隙
those uh
那些呢
those sides of the dice now what we want
骰子的那些边现在是我们想要的
to do is click on
要做的就是点击
one of the black objects in the
宇宙中的一个黑色物体
background the original polygon you'll
将原始多边形设置为背景您将
know you have it selected when you see
当你看到它时，就知道你已经选择了它
the black stripe down here in the bottom
底部的黑色条纹
left make sure you don't accidentally
离开确保你不会不小心
click the
点击
the red object click the black object in
红色对象单击中的黑色对象
the back there
后面的那个
and go to edit select same and click on
然后转到编辑，选择相同，然后点击
fill color
填充颜色
and it's going to select all three of
它将选择所有三个
those objects and we want to unify those
这些物体，我们想把它们统一起来
together so let's go to path
一起走吧，让我们去小路
union and now i'm just going to scale
联盟，现在我要扩大规模
this up a little bit
这个稍微涨了一点
if you notice here this is the reason
如果你注意到这里，这就是原因
why we're going to scale this up if you
为什么我们要扩大规模，如果您
notice here
请在此通知
the padding between the red object and
红色对象和红色对象之间的填充
the black object
黑色物体
is thinner than the padding between
比中间的填充物还要薄
these two red objects
这两个红色物体
i want to scale this up so that it
我想把它放大，这样它就
matches that oops
与之相匹配的是
matches that a little more closely i'm
更接近这一点，我是
going to hold ctrl and shift
按住Ctrl键和Shift键
and just scale it like that if yours is
就像这样扩展它，如果你的
too big you may have to scale it down
太大了，你可能得缩小一下。
just so just go ahead and manually
就这样，只要继续并手动操作
adjust it so it looks about right
调整它，使其看起来大致正确
right about there looks pretty good and
就在那里看起来很好，而且
what i want to do now is round to the
我现在想要做的是绕到
corners
转角
of this um polygon here so to do that
这个，这个多边形的，所以这样做
i'm going to add another path effect
我将添加另一个路径效果
and the path effect i'm going to look
而我将要看到的路径效应
for this time is called corners
因为这段时间被称为角落
corners philip chamfer that's what we're
角落菲利普·查姆弗这就是我们
looking for click on that
正在寻找，请点击
and i'm going to click this button right
我要点击这个按钮
here that says add a fillet or just
上面写着加鱼片或者干脆
click
单击
fill it and now i'm going to come back
装满它，现在我要回来了
over here to the edit pads by nodes tool
在此处转到按结点编辑焊盘工具
and if you notice we're going to have
如果你注意到我们将会有
these green nodes in each corner so let
每个角落里的这些绿色节点让我们
me click and drag over all of those
我点击并拖动所有这些内容
green nodes
绿色节点
let me zoom in a little bit and i'm just
让我放大一点，我只是
going to take one of those green nodes
把这些绿色节点中的一个
and just click and drag and if you
只需点击并拖动，如果您
notice it's going to round to the corner
注意，它会转到拐角处
as we do that
当我们这样做的时候
and that right there is what we're
而这就是我们正在做的
looking for that looks perfect so let me
寻找那个看起来完美的，所以让我
finalize that by going to path
通过转到Path来最终确定这一点
object to path let me grab the select
对象到路径，让我抓取选择
tool we can close out of the path
我们可以关闭小路上的工具
effects menu now we shouldn't need that
效果菜单现在我们不需要它了
again
再来一次
so we have the structure of the dice in
所以我们有了骰子的结构
place all we have to do now is color it
我们现在要做的就是给它上色
in so
在苏中
let me take this top object right here
让我把这个顶部的物体放在这里
and let me break it apart by going to
让我把它拆开，让我去
path
路径
break apart and then i want to hold
分开，然后我想要抱住
shift
换班
and click on the large red object so
点击红色的大物体，这样
that we just so that it deselects it and
我们只是为了让它取消选择它
we just have these circles selected
我们只是挑选了这些圆圈
and i want to raise those circles to the
我想把这些圈子提升到
top by clicking this button that says
点击上面的按钮，上面写着
raise selection to the top
将选定内容提升到顶部
and i'm going to make those white and i
我要把它们变成白色，然后我
want to do the same thing over here
想在这里做同样的事情吗？
select this object
选择此对象
path break apart hold shift
路径断开按住Shift键
click on that red object to deselect it
单击该红色对象以取消选择它
make these white
把这些涂成白色
and then raise them to the top and then
然后把它们举到顶端，然后
finally the same thing over here select
最后，在这里选择相同的东西
that
那
path break apart hold shift
路径断开按住Shift键
click on the object to deselect it make
单击该对象以取消选择其Make
that white
那个白色的
raise it to the top now let me zoom back
把它举到顶端，现在让我拉回
out let's click and drag over everything
让我们点击并拖动所有内容
and bring the opacity of it all the way
把它的不透明性一直带到
up so let's click off
向上，所以让我们点击关闭
to deselect everything now what we can
尽我们所能取消选择所有内容
do is we can choose
做的就是我们可以选择
colors to use for our dice i know in the
我们的骰子使用的颜色，我知道在
thumbnail i use the color green i think
缩略图我想我用的是绿色
for this one i'll use blue
这件我要蓝色的。
you can use whatever color you'd like so
你可以用你喜欢的任何颜色，所以
i'm going to start with the base back
我要从基地的后面开始
here the black object
这里是黑色物体
and start with the darker variation of
并从较暗的变种开始
whatever shade you want to use if you
你想用什么颜色，如果你
want to make your dice green start with
我想让你的骰子从绿色开始
dark green if you want to make it
如果你想做的话是深绿色的
orange start with a dark orange i'm
橙色从深橙色开始我是
going to start with a dark blue
从深蓝色开始
over here and then i'm going to click
在这里，然后我要点击
over here under the fill tab where it
在这里的填充选项卡下，它
says
说
linear gradient i'm going to click that
线性渐变，我要点击它
to give it a linear gradient
为其提供线性渐变
and then i'm going to grab the gradient
然后我要抓住渐变
tool which is over here or you can just
工具在这里，或者你可以
press
按下
g on the keyboard and if you notice we
在键盘上，如果你注意到我们
have a dark blue on this stop and we
在这一站有一个深蓝色的，我们
have transparency on this stop so let me
在这一站有透明度，所以让我
click on that stop to select it
单击该停靠点以将其选中
and i want to make this a lighter shade
我想把这件衣服改成浅色
of the color we want so since i'm using
我们想要的颜色，所以我用的是
blue i'm going to go with lighter shade
蓝色的，我要浅一点的颜色。
of blue
蓝色的
let me put this stop over here on the
让我把这一站放在这边的
bottom we want the dark one on the
底部我们想要黑暗者
bottom
底部
take this one the lighter one on top
拿这个，上面那个比较轻的。
hold ctrl bring this straight up so that
按住Ctrl键，将这个笔直向上，这样
it locks it onto the vertical axis like
它将它锁定在垂直轴上，就像
that
那
and uh it may be helpful to turn off
而且，呃，关闭它可能会有帮助
snapping at this point because snapping
在这一点捕捉是因为捕捉
we don't need it anymore and it's just
我们不再需要它了，它只是
going to get in the way from this point
从这一点开始会阻碍我们的发展
forward so
转发销售订单
up here where it says enable snapping we
在这里，上面写着启用快照
can disable that
可以禁用它
and now i want to click on this red
现在我想点击这个红色
object right here and i want to make
对象就在这里，我想要制作
this an even darker color than the dark
这是比深色还要深的颜色
shade of blue
蓝色的阴影
used over here so let me make this a
在这里用过，所以让我把它变成
dark shade of blue like that
像那样的深蓝色
that looks pretty good and let me give
这看起来很不错，让我给你
that a linear gradient
线性渐变
and i want to take this dark side and
我想把这个黑暗面
put this to the top left corner
把这个放在左上角
take this one bring it down here like
拿着这个，把它拿下来，就像
that
那
and then i want to take this object
然后我想把这个物体
right here and give that the same
就在这里，给它同样的
gradient so we'll click on linear
渐变，因此我们将单击线性
gradient and instead of creating that
渐变，而不是创建
again we can just
再一次，我们可以
choose it from this list right here it's
从这个列表中选择它，就在这里
this one we just created
这是我们刚刚创建的一个
put this one right here like that and
把这个像这样放在这里，然后
put this one down here in the
把这个放在这里
bottom right corner there we go and then
右下角，我们开始，然后
up here
在这上面
we're going to use an even lighter shade
我们将使用更浅的色调
of our color than we used for up here so
我们的颜色比我们过去在这里的颜色要好
i'm going to choose an even lighter
我要选一个更轻的
shade of blue like that
像那样的蓝色阴影
or maybe that looks pretty good and then
或者这看起来很不错，然后
we will give that a linear gradient as
我们将给出一个线性渐变为
well
井
take this and put this down here and
拿着这个，把这个放在这里
then take the transparent stop and put
然后把透明的止损放在
it up top you can hold control
在上面你可以控制它
to lock it onto the vertical axis like
将其锁定到垂直轴上，如下所示
that now let me grab the select tool let
现在让我抓起选择工具让
me zoom out a little bit
我把镜头缩小一点
if you can see our dice our vector dice
如果你能看到我们的骰子，我们的矢量骰子
is complete
是完整的
what you can do now is click and drag
您现在可以做的就是点击并拖动
over all of it
在所有这一切之上
group it together with the group
将其与组组合在一起
selected objects button
“选定对象”按钮
and i'm just going to give this a little
我只想给你一点这个
bit of a tilt to make it look like it
有点倾斜，让它看起来像
was just thrown so
就这么被抛了出去
let me select this let me click on it
让我选择这个，让我点击它
until we get the rotation handles
直到我们拿到旋转手柄
i'm going to hold ctrl and take this
我要按住Ctrl键，然后拿着这个
corner node and just bring this
拐角节点，然后把这个
counterclockwise one step
逆时针走一步
like that and then i want to right click
就像这样，然后我想右击
this and go to duplicate
这和去复制
ungroup it go to path
将其取消分组，转到路径
union and then let's make this
联合起来，然后让我们做这个
black click on it again to get back to
黑色再次单击可返回到
the scaling handles and i want to take
伸缩手柄和我想要的
this
这
arrow up here in the top in the middle
箭头向上，在上面，中间
and then just bring this all the way
然后把这个一直带到
down like that
就这样倒下了
and click the button up here that says
点击上面的按钮，上面写着
lower select lower selection to the
向下选择较低的选区到
bottom
底部
and then just bring the opacity of this
然后把这个的不透明性
down this is going to look somewhat like
往下看，这看起来有点像
a
一个
casted shadow right there that
投下的阴影就在那里
and now that is looking perfect so i
现在看起来很完美，所以我
think that should do it for this
我觉得这样就够了
tutorial that's how you can go about
教程，这就是你可以如何去做
creating these
正在创建这些
vector dice illustrations using inkscape
使用Inkscape的矢量骰子插图
if you have any questions let me know
如果你有任何问题，请告诉我
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]